UNITE Boston Joint Board Audio-Visual Materials 6000/056 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Boston Joint Board Audio-Visual Materials
1992-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/056 AV
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
7544704
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 03, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications 6000/044 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/056: UNITE Boston Joint Board Records
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Boston Joint Board; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Boston Joint Board; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7544704
- Cavanaugh's corner - Neil Rolde - 3/28/1994, 1 (Box 1)
- Cavanaugh's corner - Honduran photo-essay -- 3/14/1994, 2 (Box 1)
- A tribute to working families: we do the work, 3 (Box 1)
- Cavanaugh's Corner: Working people's electoral politics - 6/1996, 4 (Box 1)
- 1993 ACTWU Convention: Jesse Jackson, 5 (Box 1)
- It's time for a real union: it's time for UNITE!, 6 (Box 1)
- Rally for Service Employees, 7 (Box 1)
- Livelyhood - Show #1: Shift Change, 8 (Box 1)
- Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America: the Campaign of employee Rights, 9 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  a joint project of 1199 and the National Rainbow Coalition
- ACTWU- Tape #4, 10 (Box 1)
- Kaufman productions ILGWU - Window Dub Tape 1-6, 11 (Box 1)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future, 12 (Box 1)
  English/Spanish
- Danger ahead: negotiating retiree health benefits (Part 3), 13 (Box 1)
  Labor Institute of Public Affairs
- Health Care Security: Challenge to America, 14 (Box 1)
- Danger Ahead: Negotiating Retiree Health Benefits (Part 2), 15 (Box 1)
- Danger Ahead: Negotiating Retiree Health Benefits (Part 1), 16 (Box 1)
- This is far by faith: we do the work, 17 (Box 1)
- Danger Ahead: Negotiating Retiree Health Benefits: Legal issues, 18 (Box 1)
- Solidarity Day: many faces, one voice, 19 (Box 1)
- Working until it hurts: we do the work, 20 (Box 1)
- UNITE!: Because every vote counts, 21 (Box 1)
- Getting together at trend-lines: UNITE, 22 (Box 1)
  English version
- Business Ethics: Panel Discussion; NAFTA Forum, 1993; 23 (Box 1)
- Maine watch: Workers Comp, 24 (Box 1)
- Communication skills for internal organizing with Gene Morrill, 25 (Box 1)
  Labor Institute of Public affairs
- Deadly Corn, 26 (Box 1)
  This title is partial, the title is fading from the label on the tape
- Strengthen Social Security, 27 (Box 1)
- Events at Coastal Berry Co. - July 2, 1998, 28 (Box 1)
- Mark Levinson - Social Security - 3/11/1999, 29 (Box 1)
- UNITE: for the future, 30 (Box 1)
- The True cost of NAFTA, 1 (Box 2)
  Labor Institute od Public Affairs
- with George Storey, 2 (Box 2)
  This title is fading and difficult to make out
- Strengthen Social Security, 3 (Box 2)
- Sweatshops - 12/7/1996, 4 (Box 2)
- Kaufman Productions ILG: TC window dub tape 7 thru 11, 5 (Box 2)
- Kennebunkport, Maine Demonstration: Extended Unemployment Benefits, 6 (Box 2)
- LaRouche Speaks to Labor, 7 (Box 2)
- Healthext Rally, NYC, March 5, 1987: NE Regional Jt. Bd., 8 (Box 2)
- Internal Organizing Simulations, 9 (Box 2)
- ACTWU tape 5, 10 (Box 2)
- How many more must die?: Safe Jobs Now, 11 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 12 (Box 2)
- unlabeled, 13 (Box 2)
- unlabeled, 14 (Box 2)
- unlabeled, 15 (Box 2)
- Important information about your future, 16 (Box 2)
- Build homes not bombs, 17 (Box 2)
- $4 a day? No Way!, 18 (Box 2)
  American Labor Education Center
- WCSH-TV: News Report -- re: Hathaway and UNITE, 19 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#10), 20 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#9), 21 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#8), 22 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#7), 23 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#6), 24 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#5), 25 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#4), 26 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#3), 27 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#2), 28 (Box 2)
- I66 - 12/11/1992 (#1), 29 (Box 2)